Friedman, Milton Arbitration Files 5746
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Milton Friedman Arbitration Files
1967-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Friedman, Milton
5746
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3123625
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 19, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780 AV: ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5956: Archives Organization File Additional records 6021/008: Theodore W. Kheel Books and Articles
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Friedman, Milton, 1915-
3123625
- Files including Awards A-N. (Box 1)
  - C&P Telephone Company/CWA Bessette (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CUNY/PSC - Cavaliere (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CUNY/PSC (NYC Tech. Coll.) - Siemab (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Vacation Scheduling (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Long Island Hospital/District 1199 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Great A&P/Local 174 Butchers (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hunter College - CUNY/PSC - Forester (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Long Island Lighting/Local 1049 - Lineman Splicer Pay (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lan Chile Airl./IAM District 100 - Discharge (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Montclair State/AFT - Gorrin (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mt. Sinai Hospital/ District 1199 - Chui Chan Discharge (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Decision No. 68 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Decision No. 69 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Decision No. 70 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Decision No. 70 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Decision No. 72 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NYC Board of Education - Pontecorvo (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NYC Board of Education - Nurses/Therapists (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NYC Board of Education - Jackson/Coaching (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Decision No. 2 - NYC Board of Education (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NYC Board of Education - Glover (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYC Board of Education - Jorge Bermudez Comp. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NYC board of Education - Farber Resignation (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NYC Board of Education - Becker-Comp. Time (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - New York City/Lieutenant Ben. Assn. (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Files including Awards N-Z. (Box 2)
  - NYC Board of Education - M. Berger (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NY Post/Pressmen (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NY Public Library/District 37 - Comp. Time (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NY Times/Newspaper Guild Arbitrability (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NY Times/Newspaper Guild - Discharge Seabright/Lucas (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Peninsula Hospital/District 1199 - Cummings Termin. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - St. John's Hospital - Betty Schein (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Social Security Adm./ Lo. 3369 - Transportation Fee (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - UPS/Lo. 804 - Mahnken Discharge (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - UPS/Lo. 804 - Goss Disch. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - UPS/Lo. 804 - Harris Disch. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - UPS/Lo. 804 - Parez Disch. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - US Customs/NTWU, Lo. 153 Suspension (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vet Adm./Lo. 2094 - Scott Removal (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Viacom Production/Writers Guild - Violett Credit (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - West Islip Board of Education - Coach Appointment (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Western Electric/CWA 1366 Contract Issue (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Western Union/CWA (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - White Oak Ice Cream/Local 757 - Sanjou Disch. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Awards issued 1973-1982. (Box 3)
  - 1982 Awards (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1979 Awards (A-Z) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1978 Awards (A-Z) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1977 Awards (A-Z) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1976 Awards (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1975 Awards (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1974 Awards (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1973 Awards (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Awards: NYC Board of Ed./UFT 1977-1981 NYC Board of Ed./District Council 37 Paraprofessional Grievance Panel 1972-1981 NYS Colleges 1974-1979 NJS Colleges 1974-1981 State of New York 1974-1979 CUNY 1971-81. (Box 4)
  - NYC Board of Education/District 37 - Para Grievance Panel Cases (1972-81) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - New York State Cases (1974-79) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYC Board of Education/UFT Cases - 1981 Awards (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NYC Board of Education/UFT Cases (1980) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYC Board of Education/UFT Cases (1979) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYC Board of Education/UFT Cases (1978) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NYC Board of Education/UFT Cases (1976-77) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NJ State Colleges - 1981 Awards (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NJ State Colleges - 1980 Awards (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NJ State Colleges - 1979 Awards (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NJ State College - 1977 Awards (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NJ State College - 1976 Awards (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NJ State College - 1975 Awards (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NJ State College - 1974 Awards (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CUNY (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Conference and Board of Higher Education (2/16/73) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - CUNY/Professional Staff Congress and Board of Higher Education (5/14/73) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - CUNY, Professional Staff Congress and Board of higher Education (5/14/73) (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Awards: United States Steel 1971-1977 National Can 1975-1977 United Parcel Service 1972-1981 New York Hospitals 1977-1981. (Box 5)
  - NY Hospitals/District 1199 - Awards 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NY Hospitals/District 1199 - Awards 1977-79 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - IRS/NTEU (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - UPS Cases - 1972-81 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - UPS/Local 177 - IBT (Hurst Discharge) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Steel and Steelworker Awards (7106S-8685) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Steel and Steelworker Awards (9025-9956) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Steel and Steelworker Awards (10,075R-10,959) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Steel and Steelworker Awards (11,009-12,850) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National CAN Awards No. 75-1 to 75-11 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National CAN Awards No. 76-1 to 76-31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National CAN Awards Nos. 76-32 to 76-54 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National CAN Awards nos. 77-1 to 77-24 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Awards: NYC Board of Ed./UFT Paraprofessional Grievance Panel Decisions 1-67 1972-1981. (Box 6)
  - NYC Board of Education Decisions Nos. 1-14 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NYC Board of Education Decision Nos. 15-30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - NYC Board of Education Decisions Nos. 31-38 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - NYC Board of Education Decisions Nos. 39-49 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - NYC Board of Education Decision Nos. 50-64 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYC Board of Education Decision Nos. 65-67 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Awards: Miscellaneous in alphabetical order - 1967-1973. (Box 7)
  - Awards through 1972 (A-D) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Awards through 1972 (E-K) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Awards through 1972 (L-M) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Awards through 1972 (N-O) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Awards through 1972 (P-S) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Awards through 1972 (T-Z) (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Awards issued 1980-1981. One-page summary listing of contents in Boxes 1-8 58-page listing of awards and files. (Box 8)
  - 1980 Awards (A-L) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1980 Awards (M-Z) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1981 Awards (A-M) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Awards (N-Z) (Box 8, Folder 4)
- AT&T Long Lines - Bonnett Disch. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- C&P Telephone Reassignment Pay (Box 9, Folder 2)
- CUNY/PSC Davis Reappointment (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Jewish Child Care/District 1707 - Weng Suspension (Box 9, Folder 4)
- ITT Communication - Travel Time Allowance (Box 9, Folder 5)
- LIU Fac. Fed. - Release Time (Box 9, Folder 6)
- LIU - Wallace Reappointment (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Nassau Recycling/Local 729 - Working Conditions (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NYC Board of Education - Haber Pension/Salary Credit (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NYC Board of Education - Potash (Box 9, Folder 10)
- NYC Board of Education - Warkow (Box 9, Folder 11)
- NYC Board of Education - Markens P.L. Day (Box 9, Folder 12)
- NYC Board of Education - Posting (Box 10, Folder 1)
- NYC Board of Education - A. Rios Assignment (Box 10, Folder 2)
- NYC Board of Education - Letters in File (Box 10, Folder 3)
- NYC Board of Education - Wollman (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Decision No. 73 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Decision No. 74 - Medina Disch. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Decision No. 3 - Nurse Layoff (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Decision No. 76 - Richards Disch. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- NY Tel/CWA 1108 (Suffolk) (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Public Service/System Council U-2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Public Service E&G/IBEW - Grievances (Box 10, Folder 11)
- St. Mary's Hospital/District 1199 - Jagdeo Termination (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Southside Hospital/District 1199 - Full-Time Position (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Southside Hospital/District 1199 - Pasquerella Term. (Box 10, Folder 14)
- TWA/Thomas DeCanio Discharge (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Thomas DeCanio and Trans World Airlines Grievance No. 2877 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- UPS/Local 804 - Guidice Susp. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- UPS/Local 804 - McFadden Susp. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- UPS/Local 804 - Early Starts (Box 11, Folder 5)
- UPS/Local 804 - Return to Driver (Box 11, Folder 6)
- UPS/Local 804 - Supervision perf. BU Work (Box 11, Folder 7)
- UPS/Local 804 - A. Kress (Box 11, Folder 8)
- UPS/Local 804 - Ampuero Susp. (Box 11, Folder 9)
- UPS/Local 804 - Welfare Fund Contributions (Box 11, Folder 10)